class DataQuestion {
  final String questionText;
  final List<String> options;
  final int correctAnswerIndex;
  final int mark;

  DataQuestion({
    required this.questionText,
    required this.options,
    required this.correctAnswerIndex,
    required this.mark
  });
}


final List<DataQuestion> dataQuestion  = [
   DataQuestion(
    questionText: ' What is the mode in the data set {3, 7, 7, 2, 9}?',
    options: ['2', '3', '7', '9'],
    correctAnswerIndex: 2,
    mark: 5,
  ),

  DataQuestion(
    questionText: 'What is the median of the data set {5, 2, 8, 3, 7}?',
    options: ['5', '3', '8', '7'],
    correctAnswerIndex: 0,
    mark: 5,
  ),
  
  DataQuestion(
    questionText: 'What is the range of the data set {4, 8, 12, 16, 20}?',
    options: ['12', '16', '18', '16'],
    correctAnswerIndex: 1,
    mark: 5,
  ),

  DataQuestion(
    questionText: ' What is the mean of the data set {6, 8, 10, 12, 14}?',
    options: ['8', '6', '14', '10'],
    correctAnswerIndex: 3,
    mark: 5,
  ),

  DataQuestion(
    questionText: 'In the data set {2, 4, 6, 8, 10}, what is the median? ',
    options: ['8', '6', '5', '7'],
    correctAnswerIndex: 1,
    mark: 5,
  ),

  DataQuestion(
    questionText: 'If the mode of the data set is 9, which of the following sets could be the data set?',
    options: [' {4, 5, 9, 7, 8} ', ' {9, 3, 9, 4, 6}', '{5, 9, 7, 8, 10}', ' {3, 5, 7, 9, 11}'],
    correctAnswerIndex: 1,
    mark: 5,
  ),

   DataQuestion(
    questionText: 'What is the range in the data set {15, 22, 11, 8, 17}?',
    options: ['16', '12', '14', '10'],
    correctAnswerIndex: 2,
    mark: 5,
  ),

  DataQuestion(
    questionText: 'What is the mean of the data set {5, 10, 15, 20, 25}? ',
    options: ['12', '20', '18', '15'],
    correctAnswerIndex: 3,
    mark: 5,
  ),

  DataQuestion(
    questionText: 'In the data set {1, 3, 5, 7, 9, 11}, what is the median?',
    options: ['6', '5', '7', '8'],
    correctAnswerIndex: 2,
    mark: 5,
  ),

  DataQuestion(
    questionText: 'What is the mode of the data set {12, 15, 12, 18, 20}?',
    options: ['12', '15', '20', '18'],
    correctAnswerIndex: 0,
    mark: 5,
  ),

  DataQuestion(
    questionText: ' If the range of a data set is 30 and the minimum value is 10, what is the maximum value?',
    options: ['30', '40', '50', '35'],
    correctAnswerIndex: 1,
    mark: 5,
  ),

   DataQuestion(
    questionText: ' What is the median of the data set {22, 28, 24, 30, 26}?',
    options: ['22', '24', '28', '26'],
    correctAnswerIndex: 3,
    mark: 5,
  ),

  DataQuestion(
    questionText: ' In the data set {8, 12, 16, 20, 24}, what is the mode?',
    options: ['No mode', '12', '18', '16'],
    correctAnswerIndex: 0,
    mark: 5,
  ),

  DataQuestion(
    questionText: 'What is the range in the data set {45, 60, 75, 90, 105}?',
    options: ['50', '70', '80', '60'],
    correctAnswerIndex: 1,
    mark: 5,
  ),

  DataQuestion(
    questionText: 'If the mean of a data set is 10 and there are 5 numbers, what is the sum of the numbers?',
    options: ['40', '50', '80', '60'],
    correctAnswerIndex: 1,
    mark: 5,
  ),

  DataQuestion(
    questionText: ' If the range of a data set is 12 and the maximum value is 20, what is the minimum value?',
    options: ['14', '12', '8', '10'],
    correctAnswerIndex: 2,
    mark: 5,
  ),

  DataQuestion(
    questionText: 'If the range of a data set is 8 and the minimum value is 5, what is the maximum value?',
    options: ['13', '12', '18', '16'],
    correctAnswerIndex: 0,
    mark: 5,
  ),

  DataQuestion(
    questionText: 'What is the mean of the data set {3, 9, 15, 21, 27}?',
    options: ['15', '17', '16', '15'],
    correctAnswerIndex: 3,
    mark: 5,
  ),

    DataQuestion(
    questionText: 'f the mean of a data set is 8 and there are 4 numbers, what is the sum of the numbers?',
    options: ['25', '30', '32', '34'],
    correctAnswerIndex: 2,
    mark: 5,
  ),

    DataQuestion(
    questionText: 'What is the median of the data set {10, 15, 20, 25, 30}??',
    options: ['15', '20', '16', '15'],
    correctAnswerIndex: 1,
    mark: 5,
  ),
  
  

  

];